<?xml version="1.0"?>
<TeamMentor_Article Metadata_Hash="1334847491" Content_Hash="-1188817129">
  <Metadata>
    <Id>00000000-0000-0000-0000-00000061eb3b</Id>
    <Library_Id>eb39d862-f752-4d1c-ab6e-14ed697397c0</Library_Id>
    <Title>User Interface Overview</Title>
    <Category>User Interface</Category>
    <Phase>NA</Phase>
    <Technology>TEAM Mentor</Technology>
    <Type>Documentation</Type>
    <DirectLink />
    <Tag />
    <Security_Demand />
    <Author />
    <Priority />
    <Status />
  </Metadata>
  <Content Sanitized="true" DataType="markdown">
    <Data><![CDATA[TEAM Mentor provides two main avenues for accessing the vast content we offer. Each aiming at providing the answers you are looking for in the least amounts of clicks. What is the best method to use, it depends on your goal.

If you have a specific question, and know what you are looking for, then simply use the "search and filter" .

If you are not sure what you are interested in, or simply would like to browse our content, use the "Index" directory to go through a list of topics until you find one that deserves your further attention.

**The Main User Interface Has Two Areas.**

The Top Menu. Which provides access to the "Search" and "Index" functionality, as well as access to this documentation. And the workspace below which changes based on the functionality chose.

![](/Image/uioverview01.png)


**Search Page**

The default workspace is the "Search" page. Type your queries on the search bar. 

![](/Image/search01.png)

The main search page also shows your last three recently viewed articles, the three most popular trending search terms in TEAM Mentor, and the top three articles viewed on the site.
(Note that when you first sign up there will not be any recently viewed articles on the page) 

![](/Image/search02.png)


**Search Results Page**

Search Results Page displays the list of articles that match your query. The number of articles show is displayed on top.

The articles are numbered in accordance with relevance to your query. This is based on our algorithm, which is specifically tuned for InforSec questions. The algorithm is constantly being perfected to yield even more accurate results up on top.

Icon's next to the articles provide visual queues representing their relationship to a filter. 

The filters on your right help narrow down the search results. Read more about the filters [here](/article/00000000-0000-0000-0000-0000001a9296)

![](/Image/search03.png)

**Index Page**












]]></Data>
  </Content>
</TeamMentor_Article>