<?xml version="1.0"?>
<TeamMentor_Article Metadata_Hash="1640453526" Content_Hash="-1154277700">
  <Metadata>
    <Id>00000000-0000-0000-0000-00000017c916</Id>
    <Library_Id>eb39d862-f752-4d1c-ab6e-14ed697397c0</Library_Id>
    <Title>Install TEAM Mentor from a GitHub Repository</Title>
    <Category>Version Control</Category>
    <Phase>Draft</Phase>
    <Technology>TEAM Mentor</Technology>
    <Type>Documentation</Type>
    <DirectLink>Install TEAM Mentor from a GitHub Repository</DirectLink>
    <Tag />
    <Security_Demand />
    <Author />
    <Priority />
    <Status />
  </Metadata>
  <Content Sanitized="true" DataType="wikitext">
    <Data><![CDATA[This article will explain how to install TeamTeamor in a local computer from an GitHub Repository, in this case the TEAM Mentor Evaluation version which contains the full TEAM Mentor Engine and an OWASP Top 10 Library [[https://github.com/TMContent/Lib_OWASP|https://github.com/TMContent/Lib_OWASP]]

In the target machine make sure IIS and TortoiseGit is installed. (Tortoise can be installed from [[https://code.google.com/p/tortoisegit/|here]].) Also make sure you have a valid github account. No special permissions are needed for the account.
 
#Create a folder to hold your GitHub Clones. In this example we are going to use: //C:\TEAM Mentor_From_GitHub//
#In the //C:\TEAM Mentor_From_GitHub// folder right-click inside it, and chose from the Context Menu the option //'Git Clone'//
#In a browser open the page: [[https://github.com/TEAM Mentor/Master]], click on the //'Git Read-only'// button and copy the url to its right (in this case [[git://github.com/TEAM Mentor/Master.git]]). If you want to make commits from this version, you will need to use an account with push privileges to this repository.
#Back in the Git Clone Gui, put the Git url in the 'Url' TextBox ([[git://github.com/TEAM Mentor/Master.git]]) and set the 'Directory' TextBox to //'C:\TEAM Mentor_From_GitHub\Master'//). Click OK
#The //'C:\TEAM Mentor_From_GitHub\Master'// should now be populated with a number of files and folders. 
#Now you need to install the OWASP library. Follow the instructions under **Installing TEAM Mentor Library from Github** in [[article/00000000-0000-0000-0000-0000005b52c6|Installing Libraries]] and use https://[USERNAME]:[PASSWORD]@github.com/TMContent/Lib_OWASP.git ( replacing [USERNAME] and [PASSWORD] with your github credentials) in the appropriate place as described.]]></Data>
  </Content>
</TeamMentor_Article>