<?xml version="1.0"?>
<TeamMentor_Article Metadata_Hash="214964808" Content_Hash="1999839146">
  <Metadata>
    <Id>00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000803568</Id>
    <Library_Id>eb39d862-f752-4d1c-ab6e-14ed697397c0</Library_Id>
    <Title>Jade Index Navigation</Title>
    <Category>Reading</Category>
    <Phase>NA</Phase>
    <Technology>TEAM Mentor</Technology>
    <Type>Documentation</Type>
    <DirectLink />
    <Tag />
    <Security_Demand />
    <Author />
    <Priority />
    <Status />
  </Metadata>
  <Content Sanitized="true" DataType="markdown">
    <Data><![CDATA[You may choose to to browse for content is by using the "Index" page. This is useful when you would like to discover the information we have. Click on "Index" in the upper right. 

 You start to navigate the "Index" by ether selecting a subject of interest on the left, or a filter on the right. You may continue to select ether filters or subjects of interest until you find a list of articles that you would like to read. Then simply open the article by clicking on its title.

Go back to the list by using your browsers "Back" button. Some people also prefer to open articles in separate tabs, by right-clicking on the article title and selecting "Open in new tab"

Numbers next to each subject on the left represent the number of articles that exists for that subject. When you select a subject of interest. You drill down further into specific sub-topics in that subject. Narrowing down the list of articles. Bread crumb navigation on top, shows exactly where you are in the taxonomy

![](/Image/index02.png)

![](/Image/index03.png)

![](/Image/index04.png)

At any time you may select a filter on the right to narrow down the displayed list of articles further. Numbers next to the filter represent the number of articles this filter selects. 

![](/Image/index05.png)


![](/Image/index06.png)

You may also start your navigation with selecting one or more filter. Once selected, subject directory on the left updates, showing only available topics for the filter(s) 

![](/Image/index07.png)


]]></Data>
  </Content>
</TeamMentor_Article>