<?xml version="1.0"?>
<TeamMentor_Article Metadata_Hash="0" Content_Hash="0">
  <Metadata>
    <Id>00000000-0000-0000-0000-00000078b4c4</Id>
    <Library_Id>eb39d862-f752-4d1c-ab6e-14ed697397c0</Library_Id>
    <Title>Visual Studio Plugin FAQ</Title>
    <Category>Visual Studio Plugin</Category>
    <Phase>N/A</Phase>
    <Technology>TEAM Mentor</Technology>
    <Type>Documentation</Type>
    <DirectLink>Visual Studio Plugin FAQ</DirectLink>
    <Author />
    <Priority />
    <Status />
  </Metadata>
  <Content Sanitized="false" DataType="wikitext">
    <Data><![CDATA[====Is Cat.NET used behind the scenes of the TEAM Mentor Visual Studio Plugin?====
Yes the tool we integrated into TEAM Mentor Visual Studio Plug-in is Microsoft's Cat.NET v1 CTP which you can download from here [[http://www.microsoft.com/en-gb/download/details.aspx?id=19968]]

====What type of support is offered for Cat.NET tool?====
This is an official Microsoft tool and while Microsoft does not plan on releasing a new version soon, SI is now supporting the TEAM Mentor + Visual Studio + Cat.NET plug-in. Therefore SI is providing support for the Cat.NET portion of the TEAM Mentor Visual Studio Plugin.

====Is it true that Cat.NET will not work with .NET versions greater than 2.0?====
Cat.NET is able to scan all (currently released) versions of the .NET Framework (not just 2.0). Note that on the default install of the Cat.NET add-in, there is no support for Visual Studio 2010, but that is a configuration change (the TEAM Mentor Visual Studio Plugin automatically installs this Add-In and configures it accordingly)
This is a YouTube Video showing it in action: TM - Install and demo of Visual Studio Extension with Cat.NET integration v1.0 [[http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QeI3POSpAvQ]] 

====Is there a plan to integrate SI content into other scanning engines?====
From SI's and TEAM Mentor point of view, Cat.NET is just one of the scanners that we will support. We have started the integration with CheckMarx and plan to add next support for: White Hat, Fortify, AppScan Development and Standard editions, and manual security engagements. 
Here is a couple videos of our PoC of integrating TEAM Mentor with CheckMarx [[http://diniscruz.blogspot.co.uk/2012/04/poc-of-integrating-TEAM Mentor-with.html]]

]]></Data>
  </Content>
</TeamMentor_Article>