<?xml version="1.0"?>
<TeamMentor_Article Metadata_Hash="0" Content_Hash="0">
  <Metadata>
    <Id>0bfb008b-49c8-4526-bb6a-0a21d01eeb0e</Id>
    <Library_Id>eb39d862-f752-4d1c-ab6e-14ed697397c0</Library_Id>
    <Title>Quick Start Guide</Title>
    <Category>Administration</Category>
    <Phase>NA</Phase>
    <Technology>TEAM Mentor</Technology>
    <Type>Documentation</Type>
    <DirectLink>Quick Start Guide</DirectLink>
    <Author />
    <Priority />
    <Status />
  </Metadata>
  <Content Sanitized="false" DataType="wikitext">
    <Data><![CDATA[==Signing Up==
Depending on how your administrator had set up your instance of TEAM Mentor you may need to create an account. \\
Security Innovation allows 30 days of free access to [[https://www.TEAMMentor.net]] - a full version of TEAM Mentor. 

To create a TEAM Mentor account, click "Sign Up" in the top menu.

{{/Image/signup01.png}}

\\
\\

Fill in the Username, Password and E-Mail  and click Sign Up. 

Note that while creating your account you will be required to use a complex password that must fulfill the following requirements:
*At least 8 characters in length
*Have at least one decimal
*Have at least one letter
*Have at least one non-alphanumeric character

Here’s additional detail on what are considered alphanumeric and non-alphanumeric characters:
*Alphanumeric characters (word characters): a-z; A-Z; 0-9; _ (underscore); space
*Non-alphanumeric (symbols): ~`!@#$%^&*()+-_=[]\{}|;’:”,./<>?


{{/Image/signup02.png}}

\\
\\


==Accessing TEAM Mentor==

To access TEAM Mentor content, click the Login link in the top right corner. 

{{/Image/login01.png}}

\\
\\

Enter your user account credentials. After successfully authenticating, you will be able to access TEAM Mentor content. 

{{/Image/login02.png}}

\\
\\

If you have forgotten your password, click on the Forgot your password? link, fill in your email address and then a password reset email will be sent to you.

{{/Image/forgotpassword01.png}}

\\
\\

==Using TEAM Mentor==

===Searching===

The simplest way to use TEAM Mentor is by searching. The page you see immediately after login is the search page. Simply type your query in the search bar. \\
You can return to this page at any time by clicking "Search" on the top menu.

{{/Image/search01.png}}

\\
\\

The main search page also shows your last three recently viewed articles, the three most popular trending search terms in TEAM Mentor, and the top three articles viewed on the site. \\
(Note that when you first sign up there will not be any recently viewed articles on the page)

{{/Image/search02.png}}

\\
\\

Once the search results are shown, you can see the total article count. You can further narrow down the search by using one or more filters on the right. The numbers next to the filters represent the number of articles each filter selects.

{{/Image/search03.png}}

\\
\\

Icons next to the articles correspond to filters on the right. Making it easier to identify articles at a glance.

{{/Image/search04.png}}

\\
\\

You can easily remove any filter by clicking on the "X"  next to it.


{{/Image/search05.png}}


\\
\\

===Browsing==

You may choose to to browse for content is by using the "Index" page. This is useful when you would like to discover the information we have.  Click on "Index" in the upper right.

The index page is comprised of 3 main components. The subject matter taxonomy on the left, the filters on the right, and the list of available articles in the middle. 

{{/Image/index01.png}}

\\
\\

You start to navigate the "Index" by ether selecting a subject of interest on the left, or a filter on the right. You may continue to select ether filters or subjects of interest until you find a list of articles that you would like to read. Then simply open the article by clicking on its title.

Go back to the list by using your browsers "Back" button. Some people also prefer to open articles in separate tabs, by right-clicking on the article title and selecting "Open in new tab"

Numbers next to each subject on the left represent the number of articles that exists for that subject. When you select a subject of interest. You drill down further into specific sub-topics in that subject. Narrowing down the list of articles. Bread crumb navigation on top, shows exactly where you are in the taxonomy. 


{{/Image/index02.png}}

\\
\\

{{/Image/index03.png}}

\\
\\

{{/Image/index04.png}}

\\
\\

At any time you may select a filter on the right to narrow down the displayed list of articles further. Numbers next to the filter represent the number of articles this filter selects.

{{/Image/index05.png}}

\\
\\

{{/Image/index06.png}}

\\
\\

You may also start your navigation with selecting one or more filter. Once selected, subject directory on the left updates, showing only available topics for the filter(s) 

{{/Image/index07.png}}

\\
\\

As you can see, the combination of the topics and filters creates a powerful browsing mechanism that allows you to reach the desired articles quickly and intuitively. 



=Example #1 – Find Information about Cross-Site Scripting==

In the navigation pane, select the library that corresponds to the technology used by your application. For this example, we are going to use .NET 4.0 Guidance Library. Enter “Cross-Site Scripting” in the search box and click the magnifying glass search icon.

{{/Image/example1.jpg}}

The search query returns 16 results. We can read all these articles, or we can narrow the results down using filters. Let’s look for code examples by checking Code Example in the Type filter list.

{{/Image/example1-1.jpg}}

Double clicking the article will open the article in a new window:

{{/Image/example1-2.jpg}}

\\

==Example #2 – Discover Authentication Best Practices for ASP.NET 4.0==

Now let’s practice using filters. In this example, we will identify the authentication best practices for ASP.NET 4.0. It’s very simple, all we have to do is select the .NET 4.0 library and check Authentication in the Category filter list.

{{/Image/example2.jpg}}

The query returns 61 results. We can further narrow this down to show just How To articles by checking How To in the Type filter list:

{{/Image/example2-1.jpg}}

This returns a more easily managed number of items to review. Select the specific phase of development that you are currently engaged in such as Implementation or Test to narrow the results further.

{{/Image/example2-3.jpg}}

\\

==Example #3 – Finding Information on a Vulnerability (SQL Injection Example)==
One example of how you can use TEAM Mentor is to look for information you need regarding specific software vulnerabilities. This may be because you wish to avoid this vulnerability in your code, you have been assigned to fix a vulnerability, or are just looking for information on the topic. To do this, after you have successfully authenticated, Click on the //Vulnerabilities// Library in the Navigation Pane

{{/Image/example3-1.jpg}}

Select the technology from the Filters Pane. We use Java for this example. Note that the Applied Filters had been updated with your selection.

{{/Image/example3-2.jpg}}

Search for “SQL Injection” in the Search bar and hit <enter>. Note the Applied Filters was updated with your search criteria and that Article List Pane is now showing articles matching your filter selection and search criteria. Click on SQL Injection article. It will appear in the Preview Pane. Look over the description and make sure this what you are looking for. 

{{/Image/example3-3.jpg}}

Double click on the article to open it in the full article view.

{{/Image/example3-4.jpg}}

Read through the article and choose the countermeasures you want to read more about. In this case we chose to read more on Using Parametarized APIs for Data Access. Click on the link to open the article.

{{/Image/example3-5.jpg}}

Read through the article for specific information on how to fix the vulnerability.

\\

==Sharing information on vulnerability==
You may wish to share this information once you found it for collaboration on a fix, testing, or using the information to avoid that vulnerability in your code. Once you have opened a vulnerability (of any other) article you would like to share, simply copy the URL on the URL bar

{{/Image/share01.jpg}}

\\

==Saving information on vulnerability==
If you would like to save an article for later reference, after you’ve opened the article in full view, simply use your browser’s bookmarking feature to bookmark the article. The URL of articles do not change, so when you use the bookmark you will be taken right to the article. If you are not logged in, you will have to log in to see the article

\\

==Sharing a set of documents==
As you may know, content in TEAM Mentor is organized similar to playlists in music playing software. There are libraries, which contain folders, which in turn contain views. A view is a set of articles that are all related to the same topic, which is the title of the view. If you found a particular view of interest, you can focus just on the particular set of articles by using the Reading View. Simply right click on the view that you want to focus on and choose Show Reading View Link

{{/Image/share02.jpg}}

The screen will re-arrange to show the Reading View for this set of articles.

{{/Image/share03.jpg}}

You can share this view with others by simply selecting and copying the URL

{{/Image/share04.jpg}}

And pasting it into an email. When a person receives the link, when they open it they will see exactly the same set of articles, once they have logged in.

\\

==Saving a set of articles==
If you would like to save a set of articles for later reference, you can simply use your browsers functionality to bookmark the reading view.

\\

==Save filter search setting for re-use==
If you created a complex search using filters, you can save it for later reuse to get back to the same information.  Once you have selected the necessary filters. Use the pin button next to the filter in the Applied Filters box. 

{{/Image/share05.jpg}}

Clicking the button shades the pin in solid color and updates the URL in the address bar with the selected filter.

{{/Image/share06.jpg}}

{{/Image/share07.jpg}}

Use your browser to bookmark the URL,  which saves the filters for future re-use. When you click on the bookmark, it will open TEAM Mentor with the same search and filters and thus display the same set of articles.






]]></Data>
  </Content>
</TeamMentor_Article>