<?xml version="1.0"?>
<TeamMentor_Article Metadata_Hash="0" Content_Hash="0">
  <Metadata>
    <Id>0bfb008b-49c8-4526-bb6a-0a21d01eeb0e</Id>
    <Library_Id>eb39d862-f752-4d1c-ab6e-14ed697397c0</Library_Id>
    <Title>Quick Start Guide</Title>
    <Category>Administration</Category>
    <Phase>NA</Phase>
    <Technology>TEAM Mentor</Technology>
    <Type>Documentation</Type>
    <DirectLink>Quick Start Guide</DirectLink>
    <Author />
    <Priority />
    <Status />
  </Metadata>
  <Content Sanitized="false" DataType="wikitext">
    <Data><![CDATA[==Signing Up==
Depending on how your administrator had set up your instance of TEAM Mentor you may need to create an account. Security Innovation allows 2 weeks of free access to [[https://www.TEAMMentor.net]] - a full version of TEAM Mentor. 

To create a TEAM Mentor account, fill in the bolded Username, Password and E-Mail in the Selected Article pane and click Sign Up. 
Note that while creating your account you will be required to use a complex password that must fulfill the following requirements:
*At least 8 characters in length
*Have at least one decimal
*Have at least one letter
*Have at least one non-alphanumeric character

Here’s additional detail on what are considered alphanumeric and non-alphanumeric characters:
*Alphanumeric characters (word characters): a-z; A-Z; 0-9; _ (underscore); space
*Non-alphanumeric (symbols): ~`!@#$%^&*()+-_=[]\{}|;’:”,./<>?

{{/Image/signup1.jpg}}

\\

==Accessing TEAM Mentor==

To access TEAM Mentor content, click the Login link in the top right corner. 

{{/Image/login1.jpg}}

Enter your user account credentials in the Login into TEAM Mentor pop up that appears. After successfully authenticating, you will be able to access TEAM Mentor content. 

{{/Image/login2.jpg}}

If you have forgotten your password, click on the Forgot your password? link, fill in your email address and then a password reset email will be sent to you.

{{/Image/forgotpassword2.jpg}}

\\

==Using TEAM Mentor==

The simplest way to navigate TEAM Mentor content is via the navigation pane on the left. The navigation pane shows a tree representation of the available libraries as folders and views. This tree can be navigated in a manner similar to playlists in a music player, such as iTunes. 
TEAM Mentor content is organized in a manner similar to playlists. All the articles are located in the library. Views are references to sub-sets of these files. Folders are a way to organize the views. An article may appear in multiple views and folders, but there is still only one copy of the article - the views and folders display references to it.
Articles can be opened from the article list pane. Navigating the folders and views in the navigation pane changes the list of articles presented in the article list pane. The list of articles can be further narrowed down by using filters. Once the desired articles have been located, they can be previewed in the preview pane on the right by single-clicking on the article title in the list. To open the article in a new window, double-click on the article title in the list. 

{{/Image/nav1.jpg}}

\\

=Example #1 – Find Information about Cross-Site Scripting==

In the navigation pane, select the library that corresponds to the technology used by your application. For this example, we are going to use .NET 4.0 Guidance Library. Enter “Cross-Site Scripting” in the search box and click the magnifying glass search icon.

{{/Image/example1.jpg}}

The search query returns 16 results. We can read all these articles, or we can narrow the results down using filters. Let’s look for code examples by checking Code Example in the Type filter list.

{{/Image/example1-1.jpg}}

Double clicking the article will open the article in a new window:

{{/Image/example1-2.jpg}}

\\

==Example #2 – Discover Authentication Best Practices for ASP.NET 4.0==

Now let’s practice using filters. In this example, we will identify the authentication best practices for ASP.NET 4.0. It’s very simple, all we have to do is select the .NET 4.0 library and check Authentication in the Category filter list.

{{/Image/example2.jpg}}

The query returns 61 results. We can further narrow this down to show just How To articles by checking How To in the Type filter list:

{{/Image/example2-1.jpg}}

This returns a more easily managed number of items to review. Select the specific phase of development that you are currently engaged in such as Implementation or Test to narrow the results further.

{{/Image/example2-3.jpg}}







]]></Data>
  </Content>
</TeamMentor_Article>