<?xml version="1.0"?>
<TeamMentor_Article Metadata_Hash="0" Content_Hash="0">
  <Metadata>
    <Id>fa3888bd-c6d0-4f51-a4d1-0470794140b2</Id>
    <Library_Id>eb39d862-f752-4d1c-ab6e-14ed697397c0</Library_Id>
    <Title>Installation of TEAM Mentor 3.6 Back-end</Title>
    <Category />
    <Phase />
    <Technology />
    <Type />
    <DirectLink />
    <Author />
    <Priority />
    <Status />
  </Metadata>
  <Content Sanitized="false" DataType="markdown">
    <Data><![CDATA[###Add TEAM Mentor to IIS 8.0###

####Install and configure IIS (if not already installed)####

- Use the Windows Role Manager to install the HTTPS Server role.  
- Select ASP.NET 4.5 as an additional feature under .NET 4.5 Framework. 

![](/Image/install02.png)

![](/Image/install03.png)

####Add TEAM Mentor as a site in IIS.####
- Open the "Internet Information Services (IIS) Manager". 
- Navigate to the "Sites" folder in the "Connections" tree on the left. 
- Right click on the "Sites" folder.
- Select "Add Web Site...” An "Add Web Site" window should appear. 
- Enter a name for the site in the "Site name:" text box. 
- Click the "..." next to the "Physical path:" text box to set the root of the web site. A "Browse for Folder" window should appear. 
- Select to the "TM36\TeamMentor\Publish\Website.3.5" folder inside the TEAM Mentor root folder you unzipped
- Enter the hostname that TM36 will be accessible as. 
- Click "Ok". Set the port in the "Port:" text box, if necessary. 
- Click "OK".
- The "Add Web Site" window should close and a new web site should appear in the "Sites" folder in the tree on the left of the "Internet Information Services (IIS) Manager" window.
- A new web site should appear in the tree structure on the left of the "Internet Information Services (IIS) Manager" window.
 
####Set up SSL.####
 SSL is enabled by default for TEAM Mentor. Therefore it is necessary to set up SSL certificate. (Note: It is possible to disable SSL configuration)
 
First generate a CSR

- Open the "Internet Information Services (IIS) Manager". 
- Double click on the "Server Certificates" menu in the "Security" section
- From the "Actions" menu click on "Create Certificate Request."
- Follow the Wizzard to create the CSR
- Send the CSR to your Certificate Authority for Signing

Install your certificate

- Open the "Internet Information Services (IIS) Manager".
- Double click on the "Server Certificates" menu in the "Security" section
- From the "Actions" menu click on "Complete Certificate Request.
- "Browse" for your SSL Certificate file received from the Certificate Authority, then Click Next. Follow the rest of the wizard steps until finished.
- Now assign the certificate to the newly created web site. Under "Sites" Select the web site
- From the "action menu" click on "Bindings"
- Click "Add" in the window that just poped up
- Under "type" choose 'https’
- Select the certificate you just imported.
- Under “hostname” type the name URL that this site will be accessible as using HTTPS. (Note that TM40 will connect to TM36 via this URL)  
- The SSL Certificate should be the certificate you just installed.
- Click OK

####Set up Permissions####
Find the account used by IIS needs to have full control privileges to the TEAM Mentor Library_Data folder

On IIS 8 the application account name is the same as Application Pool name. This is the Windows user account used by the IIS Application Pool configured on the TEAM Mentor website.

- On the "Internet Information Services (IIS) Manager".
- Navigate to "Application Pools" in the tree on the left
- Find the Application Pool name, it will be the same as the "Site Name" you have created in step 3 above.
- Make sure that the .NET Framework version is set to v4.0. Otherwise double click on the Application Pool and set the correct version
- Take a note of the Application Pool name.
- Adjust the file-system permissions. Give full control permissions for the “\TM36\Library_Data” folder to the Windows user account that is used to run TEAM Mentor. This is the username that has been discovered in the previous step. 
    - Right click on the TEAM Mentor Library_Data folder
    - Select "Properties". A "Properties" window should appear. 
    - Select the "Security" tab in the "Properties" window..
    - Give "Full Control" to the account IIS AppPool\<AppPoolName> where the AppPoolName is the name identified above.
    - Click "OK"


]]></Data>
  </Content>
</TeamMentor_Article>